Hello there, Robbie.
What are you doing up this late?
Reading.
Reading?
At this hour?
Ah, come on, Robbie.
What are you doing up this late?
Things on my mind.
Do you care to talk about them?
Sure,
if you don't mind listening.
Robbie, Robbie, remember me? Robbie Robbie
I'm your mother.
If you have something you want to talk about,
I'm always prepared to listen.
You haven't been around much lately.
So that's it.
OK, let's talk.
You and Dad are like ships that pass in the night.
Dad works hard, and he works late.
You work hard on all your committees,
and you work late.
I thought you were proud of the work I do.
I am, Mom.
Real proud.
You are one fantastic mom,
but ... but I've been noticing
how little quality time
you spend with Dad and me ... and the family.
It's a real problem, Robbie.
I know it.
I'm concerned.
There must be a way
that Dad and you can spend more time together.
Well, we always talk about
taking a vacation together--with the family.
I think you ought to
take a vacation away from the family--alone.
Kind of a second honeymoon.
It would be wonderful,
but our schedules won't allow it.
I think I have an idea.
You do?
Yup.
I think I have an idea
that will bring Dad and you
together in a more scheduled way.
What is it?
Well,
you know how Dad is always talking about
the kids in the ward
and how important it is for them to be paid attention to?
Yes.
Well ...
and how hard it is
because the doctors and nurses are so busy?
Yes.
Well, how would it be if you took some time
to work with Dad towards solving that problem?
I don't get it.
Like setting up a regular weekly reading program.
You and Dad.
You and Dr. Philip Stewart--
going to the children's ward once or twice a week
and reading to them.
Not bad.
Not a bad idea, Robbie.
As a matter of fact,
it fits right in with something I'm working on right now
with the school-board committee.
What's that?
I've been trying
to work out a program
in the public school
that will bring parents and teachers together once a week
to read to the students--their own children, really.
By doing that, it will encourage reading.
So it might fit in with a program
for reading to the kids in the hospital.
You're right.
We'll do it!
I'm going to talk to Daddy about it right now.
But Dad was so exhausted when he came home from work.
Why don't you talk to him about it tomorrow?
You are a very smart young man, Robbie.
I think I'll wait until tomorrow.
You won't forget, will you?
Believe me, I won't.
It is a great idea,
and I promise you I won't forget.
Thanks, Mom.
Thank you, Robbie.